KEVIN LI



https://www.klix18design.com/

klix18design@gmail.com

Professional Summary

UX Designer with over 3 years of work experience at companies like NBCUniversal and Warner Bros. Discovery. Created automated systems that increased work efficiency by 500%, built websites that increased conversion rate by 200%, and designed various visual content for both digital and print.

Education

Pratt Institute

BFA Graphic Design Major UI/UX Design Minor Graduated with Highest Honors

Victoria Education

Generative AI Applications

Skills

Figma; Miro; Adobe XD; Adobe After Effects, Illustrator, Photoshop, Indesign, Premier Pro; HTML, CSS, jQuery; TouchDesigner; Arduino; Unity; Webflow; Spline; Blender; GenAl softwares; DAM, CMS

Languages

English (Native) Mandarin (Native)

Experiences

NBC Universal

UX Designer

08/2024 - present, New York

- Designed and built an automated system that reduces work time from 1 hour to 10 minutes, boosting efficiency by 500% while enhancing accuracy by minimizing human error.
- Created step-by-step, onboarding user guidelines.
- Streamlined the DAM and CMS systems for SkyShowTime to be efficient and simple to use.

Freelance

UX Designer

06/2024 - present, New York

- Lead the end-to-end design and build of Sizemore Insurance's new website, which yielded a 200% increase in leads rate, from 5% to 15%.
- Responsible for creating Sizemore Insurance's visual identity.
- Art directed and designed meta adverstisments for Sizemore Insurance in motion and still.

Warner Brothers Discovery

Contract Graphic Designer

06/2024 - present, Remote

- Art directing and creating pitch decks, album art, and end credits while handling multiple, time-sensitive requests at once.

Graphic Design Intern

06/2023 - 12/2023, Los Angeles

- Developed a broad range of design materials, including website interfaces, motion graphics, posters, signage, wayfinding, emails pitch-decks, and various show collaterals in digital and print.

Agentize.ai

Al Design Intern

03/2024 - 06/2024, Toronto

- Prompt-engineered, RAG, and fine tuned GenAI models. Crafted interactive user interfaces for hardware and software.

Relatable

Marketing Design & Video Editing Intern

06/2022 - 06/2022, New York

- Designing Youtube, Amazon, Target, and Instagram advertisments in motion and still.

NI V/ I